When all these other regions climbed into our Kursk region, they
Когда у нас на курскую область полезли
beat us up.
все эти другие области на нас забили
Excuse me on my word, that’s all I have,
Извини на слове вот и всё у меня у меня
my guy is a Paratrooper. They
у меня дядька он Десантник Они под
are standing near Lgovo now and are holding the defense,
Льгово стоят сейчас да держат оборону
so says Donetsk Lugansk when it
так говорит Донецк Луганск когда
started in Donetsk Lugansk they were throwing ours,
началось в Донецк Луганск кидали наших
here he is  he was a paratrooper, his brigade was
вот он был десантником его бригаду
abandoned Yes, how many boys were killed now, no
кидали Да сколько пацанов полегло сейчас
one from Donetsk and from Lugansk were thrown
никого с Донецка и с Луганска не кинули
into the defense of the Kursk region
на оборону Курской области
Hello Hello, where are you
здравствуйте Здравствуйте а вы с Вы
from? We are from Russia Oh well, I’m
откуда Мы с Россией Да ладно Я тоже я их
trolling them too In short, I hung up the flag, they shout
троллю Короче я повесил флаг они кричат
Glory to
Слава
Ukraine Where are you from?  What
Украине Вы откуда А вы от Из какого
city are you from? We're from grove near
города Вы откуда Мы с гров рядом с
Kursk You just saw the forty-sixth and
Курском Вы видели просто сорок шестой и
that's why you say that No no it's true We're
поэтому так говорите Нет нет правда Мы
grove really in groves
гров правда в гровс
learning a program No it's true here Find
учимся прогу Нет правда вот Найдите
okay the truth you can find where it's scary
ладно правда можете найти откуда страшно
Well I'm from Kursk itself Yes okay Yes  I have
Ну я из Курска самого Да ладно Да у меня
a grandmother in the Sudzhansky district, but we managed to
бабушка в суджанском районе но мы успели
get her out.
её вывести
Eun Who’s there, he’s drunk, yes I understand You’re 18
Ын Кто там он пьяный да понял Вам по 18
years old, damn it, and you’re calm
лет есть есть блин а у вас спокойненько
there With us, yes, as well as in the course
там У нас да как и в курс
No, well, like in Kursk, wait, we
Не ну как в Курске подожди у нас тут
had a drone fly in here Well  this was a long time ago
было беспилотник прилетал Ну это давно
on the allied one when he flew in,
было на союзную когда прилетал
hearing everything Dim, that maybe it’s some kind of
это слыша всё Дим что это какой-то может
short damn thing you have and you don’t
у вас короче блин какой-то а вы не в
know. He’s
курсе Он он вас
baiting you from your region, I can show you the
байтит шего региона я могу показать
forty-sixth region. Let him show you the
сорок шестого регио Пусть он покаже
forty-sixth region of some kind.  we even
сорок шестого региона какой-то даже
communicate normally damn Kursk region
нормально общаемся блин Курской области
Listen Let's girls look if we
Слушай Давайте девчонки смотри если мы
speak Normally we speak normally
говорим Нормально мы говорим нормально
If not I'll go further to troll
Если нет я пойду дальше ло троллить
Koche showing Masha's number and what I can
коче показа номер Маши и что я те могу
also find in Ukraine From the
тоже найти в Украине Со номер
region number Dude this is the number from my Cars where are you
региона Чувак это номер с моей Тачки ты
from
откуда
Let's show  number try CBI
Давай покажи номер пробей цби
in short de
короче де
well look
ну посмотри
try where is my
пробей где мой
phone try also Telegram provet
телефон пробей тоже Telegram провет
Mitsubishi If it's the ninety-eighth year
Mitsubishi Коль девяносто восьмой год
what what Mitsubishi Mitsubishi If it's the
чего какой Mitsubishi Mitsubishi Коль
ninety-eighth year my car And why does
девяносто восьмой год моя тачка А почему
he have a language and not a Russian language, this is your
у него мова а не русская это у тебя
language, look Let him enter enter in
мова смотри Пусть он вводит введи в
Telegram 705  705 705
Telegram 705 705 705
we check Damn it’s absolutely
проверяем Блин вообще
terrible, we’re
ужас мы
kind, so look at the registration
добри тож посмотри там регистрация
Kursk in 1998. We’ve
Курская девяносто восьмого года Всё
checked everything. We just believe He’s aggressive,
проверили Мы верим просто Он агрессивный
damn it. Show the lock on the phone,
какой-то блин Покажи локу на телефоне
oh my. In short, listen, let’s send him to the
ё-моё Короче слушай давай его посылай в
bathhouse, he’s tired of it already,
баню он задолбал уже
section will tell me to show
разд скажет показать
my owner
мой владелец
and
а
that you can please show the vacations
что можешь пожалуйста показать вакации
on your phone so that he calms down the geolocation
на телефоне чтобы он успокоил геолокацию
that Yes, I won’t let him, damn him, why do I
что Да не буду я ему пусть он блин зачем
even need him, you’re cool girls, I’m
мне он вообще вы классные девчонки Я с
communicating normally with you, damn you now,
вами нормально общаюсь блин вам сейчас
damn it, bring it in short, show your wife,
блин блин привезти короче жену показать
damn it, so she can also show you your passport, your
блин чтобы она ещё паспорт показала вас
wife has it  Bring your wife to eat Listen,
жена есть жену Привози есть Слушай что
he says some nasty things
он гадости он какие-то гадости говорит
to me and my daughter, my wife is beautiful My name is What is
мне с дочкой жена красавица Меня зовут
your name Angelina Why does he
Тебя как зовут Ангелина Зачем он такие
say such nasty things about his daughters, why do
гадости про дочек говорит ну зачем такое
I Nastya, you understand how he behaves
я Настя он как себя ведёт понимаешь
Nice to meet you Nastya and Angelina
Приятно познакомиться Настя и Ангелина
Cool yes And you  What are you
Прикольно да А вы на Медиков на кого
studying to become a nurse?
учитесь именно на медсестёр
It's cool nurse, you're the one who's going to give
прикольно медсестра это вы будете
injections,
укольчики делать будем
yes, and you're also a nurse, a guy
да а это у вас тоже медбрат пацан
who's aggressive, no, oh,
который агрессивный нет ой
and who he's
а на кого он
studying to be, we don't
учится мы не
know, I
знаем
understand you a lot, the Ukrainians are trolling, they're
понял вас сильно тут украинцы троллят
probably yelling at you
орут наверно вас
right away, I'm like me  I did the same thing. Here
сразу я типа как я же типа сделал Вот у
I have this chromakey like this Green background
меня это хромакей типа это Зелёный фон
they shout in short Glory to Ukraine they are so
они короче кричат Слава Украине такие
kind right away I show them that I am
добрые сразу Я им показываю что я ику
right away they turn on they start
сразу у них включается они начинают
buddy I don’t even understand that they are
дружище я вообще я не понимаю что они на
angry with us you are angry buddy you are from
нас злятся злятся дружище ты из
Kursk listen look  if we're talking we're
Курска слушай смотри если мы говорим мы
talking if this dude wants to
с вами говорим если этот чувак хочет
talk Let him sit here with me and
говорить Пусть он сядет сюда со мной
talk to me Yes, he's not all
поговорит Да не он всё
like me I'll send him in short and I'll
подоб я Я его я его пошлю короче и всё и
switch everything And in which area In the course is
переключу А каком районе В курс
normal Look at Sumskaya I live
нормально Смотри на Сумской Я живу е
like Klykova  you again, let's
а Клыкова как вам ещё раз давай мы
talk normally if ho if this
нормально поговорим если хо если этот
dude wants it's his problem Let him let him let
чувак хочет это его проблемы Пусть он
him Look, he told me to
вят пусть он вят Смотри он он мне сказал
punch the number, punched the number Well, that's all mits
номер пробить пробил номер Ну всё mits
Since the eighth year, my registration is
Коль дено восьмого года мой регистрация
Kursk, everything that they need to show him what else toilet
Курская всё что им ему что ещ туалетную
paper  or that some people are damn
бумагу показать или что какие-то блин
inadequate, damn if we yell at our own people
неадекваты блин если Мы свои на своих
like that In short, like at a spy,
будем так орать Короче как на шпиона
damn it, then of course, damn it, they’ll reach Kursk
блин то конечно блин до Курска дойдут
because we’re ready to devour
блин потому что мы готовы сожрать друг
each other, you know, we’re
друга понимаешь
ready, that’s all, because when we
готовы вот и всё потому что когда у нас
all got into the Kursk region  these
на курскую область полезли все эти
other regions have scored on us Sorry for the
другие области на нас забили Извини на
word, that’s all I have, my
слове вот и всё у меня у меня у меня
guy is a Paratrooper. They are standing near Lev
дядька он Десантник Они под Львом стоят
now and holding the defense,
сейчас да держат оборону
so he says from Donetsk Lugansk when it
так говорит с Донецк Луганск когда
started in Donetsk Lugansk they threw ours,
началось в Донецк Луганск кидали наших
he was a paratrooper, they threw his brigade Yes,
вот он был десантником его бригаду
how much  the boys were killed now,
кидали Да сколько пацанов полегло сейчас
no one from Donetsk and no one from Lugansk, no one was thrown
никого с Донецка и с Луганска не кинули
into the defense of the Kursk region,
на оборону Курской области
that’s all. But we are Kurians among ourselves, you
никого вот и всё А мы между собой куряни
understand
понимаешь
And we have these Chechens who stood
И у нас вот эти чеченцы что стояли
shorter, I don’t know if they
короче вот не знаю ли они у вас типа
were in your town, like, yes, here we are  they all
были в городке Да у нас типа вот они всё
cut us through restaurants so cool
они по ресторанам рассека такие крутые
and when in short
да когда короче
where are these Chechens where ahma who is
где эти чеченцы где ахма кто на
filming us for tiktoks they
за тиктоки снимают нас кинули вот
just cheated me I say my
просто меня я говор у меня
father is near Lev and desan An uncle is in the
отец под Львом да десан Дядька в
Donetsk region now why should he from
Донецкой области сейчас почему он из
Kursk defend the Donetsk region
Курска должен защищать донецкую область
when the Kursk  the region is not protected My
когда курскую область не защищают У меня
mother is afraid to go to work,
мама боится ходить на работу
she is a pensioner now Yes, but she goes to
она пенсионер сейчас Да но она ходит на
work She is a teacher in a kindergarten and she
работу Она в садике воспитатель и она
says damn they can fly in to us, what does she
говорит блин нам может прилететь что она
say, what will I do if
говорит что я сделаю если будет прилёт
hail arrives, how will I protect these children in the
града что как я защищу этих детей в
kindergarten and no one  everyone was shouting in short
садике и никто вот все орали короче вот
here Well done Let's be like this until the end And
там Молодцы Давайте до конца такие А
when trouble came to the Kursk region everyone
когда на курскую область пришла беда все
disappeared Muscovites are all hanging out in clubs
пропали Москвичи все тусят по клубам
Donetsk Lugansk also short of us Crimea ate
Донецк Луганск тоже нас короче Крым ели
They swim in the sea Yes they are in short
Они купаются в море Да им короче вот
I just met a guy from Crimea here I
просто я встречал тут чувака с Крыма
tell him too  Listen, Damn, why
тоже ему говорю Слушай Блин а что вы
don’t you write down Crimea for us for the people of
типа Крым никак не вписывай за нас за
Kursk, they say like you and so
курян они говорят типа вас и так защитит
Putin will protect you, in short, and so on, they think that
Путин короче и так дальше они думают что
everything here is chocolate, they are in Crimea
у нас тут всё в шоколаде они в Крыму
Damn, they don’t have Ukrainian troops in Crimea,
Блин у них в Крыму украинских войск нету
but we have  I have a neighbor in the Kursk region. I have a
А у нас в Курской области есть У меня
neighbor,
соседка то
she has a grandmother from the Glushkovsky district.
у неё с глушковского района
Why, the [ __ ] idiot from Ukraine, the Armed Forces,
бабушка Да что задолба с Украины ВС
is nervous. Dude, you should
нервничает Чувак ты бы свою энергию
use a little of your energy to help Russia instead
немножко пустил на помощь России вместо
of this Glushkovsky trolls
того чтобы вот это тролли глушковского
rana evacuating them, too, evacuating where
рана эвакуирует их тоже эвакуирует куда
she came to her home.  grandma from the
она приехала к ней домой У меня бабка с
Sudzhansky district Like she’s
суджанского района Типа она вот у нас
been living with us for a month already Why Because
уже живёт месяц Почему Потому что там
damn it We didn’t leave her in the first days and they
блин Мы же е не оставили в первые дни е
took her away And from what district is Sudzhi not mom
забрали А с какого района суджи не мама
but grandma Bausch grandma mom mom in
а бабушка бауш бабушка мама мама в
Kursk already the
Курске уже здоровье
grandma’s health of course And you’re scared of this  everything is
бабу конечно И вам страшно это всё
scary Let's not talk about the war,
страшно Давайте не будем про войну
let's have hookahs in Kursk
давайте у меня в Курске есть кальяны
Come, I'm not the hookahs, that's not
Приходите не я кальяны не
it You have hookah, hold it Well,
это Это у вас есть калья пр держишь Ну
yes, Well, I'm with a young man Well, I understand, I
да Ну я с молодым человеком А ну понял Я
think that, well, how are you studying to be a nurse
думаю что ну как ты учишься на медсестру
and you're
и Коляну
holding Kolyana damn it  what kind of whisperer is there with tell me
держишь блин что там за шептун с скажи
if he wants a hookah bar on Karl Marx
если он хочет кальянную на Карла Маркса
77 to a hookah bar I know, in short, I
77 к кальянная под знаю я короче по
don’t know about hookahs, he works. This is
кальянам не шарю работает Это брат
Albina’s brother. Well, okay, what kind of Albina’s brother?
Альбины Ну ладно что за брат Альбины
Yes, a boy works for us, the girl’s brother
Да у нас работает мальчик брат девочки
who studies with us, too, already like-  it’s
который учится у нас тоже в уже как-то
hard, boy,
тяжело мальчик брат
girl’s brother, yes And you have one of your
девочки да А у тебя кто-то из
relatives, why do
родственников на сво есть
I have a dad too And where is he at least? Well, in the
очем у меня батя тоже А он где хоть Ну в
Kursk region or his Lord I mean
Курске область или его Господи В смысле
how old is 59 How old is he 59 years old and what And he’s
сколько 59 Сколько лет 59 лет и что А он
a career military man,
Кадровый военный
well, 60  For years now, in my opinion, it’s impossible to do that, he’s a
это ну 60 лет уже по-моему нельзя так он
career military man, he’s not mobile, he’s a
Кадровый военный он не мобили он
career military man, you can be there. He’s a
Кадровый военный там можно Он
contract worker.
контрактный
And he’s been a military man all his life because
А он он всю жизнь военным был потому что
he’s a damn guy and after all he’ll be
ему блин он и после ше будет он
like that Ponya.
такой Поня А вас очима в какую область
I don’t know exactly what region you were thrown into.  I just don’t
бросили точно не знаю я просто не с
live with my parents, well, like, not in the Kursk
родителями живу ну типа не в Курской
region, dates
области дат
in Kursk, well, that’s it, that we have
в Курской там ну вот это да что у нас
a lot of men, my dad says
очень многих мужиков у меня батя говорит
Yes, they also took their divisions and
Да что с ихней Дивизии тоже взяли
transferred a bunch of people, like, well, somewhere
перебросили куча людей типа ну куда-то
there in Donetsk Lugansk Kherson he  says the
туда на Донецк Луганск Херсон он говорит
dudes, half of them have traveled around the
чуваки половина из них объехали вот так
entire combat zone like this and in Kherson they
всю зону боевых действий и в Херсоне
are sitting here in Kursk, a breakthrough is coming Yes, they are
сидят тут в Курск прорыв идёт Да они
their wives, it turns out there are wives, children
ихние жёны тут получается есть жёны дети
like in a jacket, they need to be protected here, they
типа в куртке их надо тут защищать они
are sitting somewhere there
где-то там сидят
manicure You have
маникюр У тебя
a cool one too I  I say
классный никакой тоже Я же говорю
cool Because when you know And what is
классный Потому что когда знаеш А как
your name Andrey And what Andrey And you can
вас зовут Андрей А что Андрей А можете
remove the flag it’s unpleasant to talk,
убрать флаг неприятно разговаривать
you know, it’s green background I can’t
понимаете это ж Зелёный фон я его не
remove it I can’t there my program
убрать я не могу там у меня программа
is set up everything will go wrong I’m telling you
настроена всё собьётся Я же тебе говорю
that I’m trolling me
что я троллю у меня
configured specifically for trolling,
настроено специально для троллинга
in short, they come out like this right away hurray hurray like
короче выходят такие сразу ура ура типа
I'm
я
like that I'm undermining them so Well
такой их подрываю так что Ну
yes it is And what are you afraid of this flag Well
да такое А что вы боитесь этот флаг Ну
damn it hung up God it's necessary and you'll troll you'll
что блин повесил Боже нужно и ты будешь
hang it up God what's the difference We
троллить повесишь Боже какая разница Мы
won't have that kind of weight our guys over there are also
не будем такой вес наши вон ребята тоже
on  at the front they are camouflaged, like they are raising
на фронте маскируются типа поднимают
this Ukrainian flag, like they think that they are
этот украинский флаг типа те думают что
their own. In short, they shoot everything is all normal for the
свои Короче они стреляют всё всё норм в
purpose,
целях
in short, it’s
короче
normal. Well, okay, we’ll move on.
нормально Ну ладно мы пойдём дальше
Let’s Slava
Давайте Слава
[laughter]
[смех]
Ukraine write to my Telegram straight away from the
Украине пись на мий Telegram прям зараз
VN axis and
ось ВН а
Popik is very and very polite YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
busy  us through skarg Orki in your ban and even
заня нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и
more videos are not shown to people
дуже багато видео не показуе людям
immediately not yet the
вчасно не пока
information is simple for that for that, for that purpose, Mali
информа прост тому для того щоб ми Мали
operational link ppi directly immediately and while
оперативный звязок ппи прямо зараз а пок
there in telegra okm video esh tezh tsikava and korisna
там в телегра окм вдео ще теж цикава и
information and we are sorry for you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati postiyniy  operational connection is
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
not important in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава украини пись
L
L